# PERSIJANENKO KYRYLO

## Senior Full Stack Developer

### SUMMARY

Passionate Software Engineer with 10+ years of experience in developing web applications and backend systems. Skilled at writing clear, concise code that is easy to maintain and troubleshoot. Experienced in working with both small and large teams across multiple projects and companies. When working on a project, you will always be passionate, challenging, and show a sincere attitude that will do everything you can to solve the problem.

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## Full-Stack Web Developer

2021 - Present

#### Upwork.com

www.upwork.com/

 As a Full stack Software Developer, I have been involved in several projects and successfully completed two projects.

## Senior Software Engineer

2019 - 2021

.K.I.S.S. Software

Kiev office Moskovska St, 8, Kyiv, Ukraine, 02000

applications using the node is framework.

Based on solid knowledge of React, Vue, Angular, node is, and typescript, I have

As a Senior Software Developer, I have developed and completed numerous web

- Based on solid knowledge of React, Vue, Angular, node.js, and typescript, I have developed various websites, including e-commerce and CRM.
- By conducting automation tests for web applications, we saved the cost of project testing and became a QA automation developer.
- In addition, he participated in various fields such as .Net core, Springboot, and Chat-GPT AI, leaving an outstanding experience as a senior software engineer.

### Software Developer

2015 - 2017

inVerita

Ivana Franka street, 102, Lviv, Lviv region, Ukraine, 79000

- As a Junior Software Developer, I have gained a wealth of experience through extensive involvement in front-end web page development.
- Created numerous UI/UX pages using front-end frameworks such as React.js, Vue.js, and Angular.js.

## **EDUCATION**

National University of Civil Protection of Ukraine

2015 - 2021

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE & WEB DEVELOPER

61023, Kharkov, st. Chernyshevskaya, 94



### **SKILLS**

#### Front-end stacks

 $\mathsf{React.js} \cdot \mathsf{Vue.js} \cdot \mathsf{Next.js} \cdot \mathsf{Nust.js} \cdot$ 

Angular.js · Svelte.js · HTML · CSS ·

Javascript

### Back-end stacks

Node.js · Express.js · Nest.js · Typescript ·

 $\mathsf{PHP} \boldsymbol{\cdot} \mathsf{Laravel} \boldsymbol{\cdot} \mathsf{Wordpress} \boldsymbol{\cdot} \mathsf{Springboot} \boldsymbol{\cdot}$ 

ASP.net core · Razor · Python · Django ·

Flask

### Database designer

 $MySQL \cdot SQLite \cdot PostgreSQL \cdot MongoDB \cdot$ 

MariaDB · FireBase · AWS RDS ·

SQL server

### Third parties & REST APIs

Google APIs · AWS web services · Azure

## **LANGUAGES**

English:

Russian:

Ukrainian: